The hottest action ever to hit the slopes.
Ski School is a comedy film directed by Damian Lee.
Rival groups in a skiing school do battle on and off the piste.
One gang are rich and serious, the other group are party animals.
Dave Marshak, played by Dean Cameron.
John E. Roland, played by Tom Bresnahan.
Ed Young, played by Patrick Labyorteaux.
Reid Janssens, played by Mark Thomas Miller.
Derek Stevens, played by Spencer Rochfort.
Lori, played by Darlene Vogel.
Ski School is a 1991 comedy film directed by
Damian Lee and starring Dean Cameron.
Its plot concerns a fictional ski school.
A sequel, Ski School 2, followed in 1994, also starring Cameron.
The film explores themes of sports, rivalry, snow skiing, ski resort.
The tone is lighthearted.